<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>STRAPS 2020</title><link>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/</link><atom:link href="https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>STRAPS 2020</description><generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><image><url>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/img/network.jpg</url><title>STRAPS 2020</title><link>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/</link></image><item><title/><link>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/author/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/author/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="building-edge-and-fog-applications-on-the-fogstore-platform">Building edge and fog applications on the FogStore platform&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Today’s applications in domains such as the Internet of Things are no longer cloud-based. Instead, they often rely on edge and fog resources to address latency and privacy requirements or to deal with bandwidth limitations. Handling the complexity of such environments, however, often exceeds the capabilities of the average software developer. In this talk, we will give an overview of the FogStore platform and the abstractions it provides which significantly eases the development of applications that go beyond cloud-only deployments.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/Users/Ge/Desktop/bermbach/158px-Davidbermbach.jpg" alt="158px-Davidbermbach">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>David Bermbach&lt;/strong> is an Assistant Professor at TU Berlin and at the Einstein Center Digital Future in Berlin, Germany where he is heading the Mobile Cloud Computing research group. In his research, he is working on platforms and applications for cloud, edge, and fog computing, systems benchmarking, as well as interdisciplinary research topics. David has a Diploma in business engineering and a Ph.D. with distinction in computer science both from Karlsruhe Institute of Technology, Germany.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/author/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/author/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="enabling-interactivity-between-human-and-artificial-intelligence">Enabling Interactivity between Human and Artificial Intelligence&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Interactivity is to enable users to interact with their data and data systems effectively. It goes beyond efficiency measures and aims to make data usable for users. There exist different needs to interact with data and seek relevant information for an improved decision making process, such as shopping online, finding risky insured drivers, and building expert committees. In this talk, we discuss challenges and opportunities to substantiate interactivity in artificial intelligence applications. We begin by introducing the status quo, i.e., AI systems in which the user is left out of the loop, such as automated end-to-end ML pipelines, which lack personalization, customization, and explanation. Then we present a “guidance” approach in the form of a mixed-initiative system, where both human intelligence and artificial intelligence assist each other through iterative interactions to achieve higher levels of effectiveness. Next we describe how Reinforcement Learning helps model these interactions and how learned policies can augment the quality of interactions. Last, we discuss some results obtained so far and some future directions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://straps-workshop.github.io/2020/Users/Ge/Desktop/omidvar-tehrani/Unknown.jpeg" alt="Unknown">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Behrooz Omidvar-Tehrani&lt;/strong> is a Research Scientist with a focus on interactive data systems. He has held positions in Naver Labs Europe, the Grenoble Alpes University, and the Ohio State University. His research interest is in the area of data management and at the crossroad of data mining, databases, and machine learning. He has published several papers in international conferences, such as VLDB, SIGMOD, and ICDE, and journals such as TKDE, VLDBJ, and FGCS.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>